Privacy Policy
==============

**Consent**
-----------

By subscribing to our services, you agree and accept that we may gather, process, store and/or use the personal data submitted in accordance with the rules set below.

**What information do we collect ?**
------------------------------------

**When you are on MailReach’s website**  

**For statistics** : when you are using the MailReach services, we may track your browsing activity by using Google Analytics.  

**For user contact info and details** : when you signup to MailReach, we ask you to fill your email, first name, postal address, city, country, login, password.  

**For invoicing and payments** : When you subscribe to a paid plan, we collect your payment information to send it to our provider Stripe, Inc. We will never save or put your payments information to a database or on our own servers. Only Stripe, Inc saves and collects those information.  

**When you are using MailReach warmup service**
-----------------------------------------------

**Logging and history events** : Once you become a MailReach customer we monitor your usage, and log any requests you will do to our service. All those logs captured by the MailReach service may include IP address, geolocalization information, browser type, computer type, country etc.  

**Email deliverability activity and mailbox tracking** : in order to help you monitor your deliverability improvements, we count the number of warmup emails (= emails sent by MailReach) sent in inbox, spam or categories and the number of warmup emails received in inbox, spam or categories.  

**Email contact details** : in order to personalize the content of warmup emails, we use the first name and last name of the email account you gave us access to.  

**What do we do with your personal information ?**
--------------------------------------------------

MailReach collects your personal data fairly and lawfully and in accordance with any applicable law including the General Data Protection Regulation. The main purpose of collecting personal data is to provide you with a safe, optimal, efficient and personalized experience.  

We may use your personal data to :  

* **Give access to our service** : When creating an account, you agree to our Terms of Use which allow us to process your data to give you access to MailReach.
* **Online customer support:** We offer and include free customer support via email or via chat, to help you to use the MailReach service or fix issue you may find while using the service.

Summer Sale: Get **20% OFF** for the first 30 days of warming up your first mailbox – [**Start now**](https://app.mailreach.co/signup?utm_content=top-bar) 🎉

Blog

[Login](https://app.mailreach.co/signin)[Sign up

Sign up](https://app.mailreach.co/signup)

[Login](https://app.mailreach.co/signin)[Sign up

Sign up](https://app.mailreach.co/signup)

[

MailReach x Stripe Climate](https://climate.stripe.com/Y1e1kL)

Quick Links

Great Resources

Legal

Support

Copyright 2024. All rights reserved
